{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857793776","data":{"timestamp":" 947857793774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857802039","data":{"timestamp":" 947857802039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857823869","data":{"timestamp":" 947857823869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857830458","data":{"timestamp":" 947857830458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857838005","data":{"timestamp":" 947857838005"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857848717","data":{"timestamp":" 947857848715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857855346","data":{"timestamp":" 947857855346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857862927","data":{"timestamp":" 947857862927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857869514","data":{"timestamp":" 947857869513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857876115","data":{"timestamp":" 947857876115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857882717","data":{"timestamp":" 947857882716"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857889303","data":{"timestamp":" 947857889303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857895923","data":{"timestamp":" 947857895923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857903342","data":{"timestamp":" 947857903342"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857909945","data":{"timestamp":" 947857909945"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857916566","data":{"timestamp":" 947857916566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857925572","data":{"timestamp":" 947857925572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857937193","data":{"timestamp":" 947857937193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857947808","data":{"timestamp":" 947857947807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 1c8d9adc-dccc-417c-91d5-3dd07e09ba52"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857968711","data":{"timestamp":" 947857968711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857975316","data":{"timestamp":" 947857975315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857982850","data":{"timestamp":" 947857982850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947857993505","data":{"timestamp":" 947857993505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858000108","data":{"timestamp":" 947858000108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858006711","data":{"timestamp":" 947858006711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858014167","data":{"timestamp":" 947858014166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858020771","data":{"timestamp":" 947858020771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858027380","data":{"timestamp":" 947858027379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858033981","data":{"timestamp":" 947858033981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858041415","data":{"timestamp":" 947858041415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858048051","data":{"timestamp":" 947858048051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858054622","data":{"timestamp":" 947858054622"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858062073","data":{"timestamp":" 947858062072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858070924","data":{"timestamp":" 947858070924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 5779a750-6ad9-4c7c-8f5c-a0d2c94cb7f3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858094265","data":{"timestamp":" 947858094265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858100876","data":{"timestamp":" 947858100874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858108424","data":{"timestamp":" 947858108424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858119029","data":{"timestamp":" 947858119029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858125650","data":{"timestamp":" 947858125650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858133169","data":{"timestamp":" 947858133169"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858143794","data":{"timestamp":" 947858143794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858149986","data":{"timestamp":" 947858149986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858156623","data":{"timestamp":" 947858156623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858164162","data":{"timestamp":" 947858164162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858170763","data":{"timestamp":" 947858170763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858177406","data":{"timestamp":" 947858177406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858184061","data":{"timestamp":" 947858184061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858190679","data":{"timestamp":" 947858190679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858197304","data":{"timestamp":" 947858197304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858206187","data":{"timestamp":" 947858206186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 29540596-b9a7-44bb-a66b-299808e6a911"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858228326","data":{"timestamp":" 947858228325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858234964","data":{"timestamp":" 947858234964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858241618","data":{"timestamp":" 947858241617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858248272","data":{"timestamp":" 947858248272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858254910","data":{"timestamp":" 947858254910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858261573","data":{"timestamp":" 947858261573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858268203","data":{"timestamp":" 947858268202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858274841","data":{"timestamp":" 947858274841"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858281497","data":{"timestamp":" 947858281497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858288120","data":{"timestamp":" 947858288119"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858301162","data":{"timestamp":" 947858301162"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 142bb4e2-d995-4150-a58f-9d77f5f4545a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858323218","data":{"timestamp":" 947858323218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858329872","data":{"timestamp":" 947858329872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858336510","data":{"timestamp":" 947858336510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858343165","data":{"timestamp":" 947858343165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858349856","data":{"timestamp":" 947858349855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858356761","data":{"timestamp":" 947858356760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858363598","data":{"timestamp":" 947858363596"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858370520","data":{"timestamp":" 947858370519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858377413","data":{"timestamp":" 947858377412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858384350","data":{"timestamp":" 947858384349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858397732","data":{"timestamp":" 947858397731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e4602334-b8c6-4743-9fe0-f3f24a7a0847"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858423103","data":{"timestamp":" 947858423103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858431287","data":{"timestamp":" 947858431286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858438410","data":{"timestamp":" 947858438409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858445518","data":{"timestamp":" 947858445517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858452681","data":{"timestamp":" 947858452680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858459813","data":{"timestamp":" 947858459813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858466971","data":{"timestamp":" 947858466969"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858474146","data":{"timestamp":" 947858474145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858481315","data":{"timestamp":" 947858481314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858488511","data":{"timestamp":" 947858488510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858495685","data":{"timestamp":" 947858495684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858509102","data":{"timestamp":" 947858509101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 619031dd-0875-4390-b64d-07912fd909a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858534865","data":{"timestamp":" 947858534864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_sijaiona_siwezi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858541998","data":{"timestamp":" 947858541997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sifa_sifa_sisi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858549130","data":{"timestamp":" 947858549129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" simu_simba_simu_simama"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858556317","data":{"timestamp":" 947858556316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sina_sina_sijawahi_siyo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858563485","data":{"timestamp":" 947858563485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_simba_sitawahi_sisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858570755","data":{"timestamp":" 947858570754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_simu_sikio_siyo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858577916","data":{"timestamp":" 947858577915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sijawahi_sisi_sinsou"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858585071","data":{"timestamp":" 947858585070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" siafu_siafu_sivyo_siwezi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858592271","data":{"timestamp":" 947858592270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" sisi_siafu_sisi_sivyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858599577","data":{"timestamp":" 947858599577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.si.show.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858613083","data":{"timestamp":" 947858613082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" fc8e91d7-870d-400f-aa62-f116ca800ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.si.show.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_sinsou_simama_siku"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858628229","data":{"timestamp":" 947858628228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 253860ef-d859-44b9-af2b-fc6d279b0e1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858628470","data":{"timestamp":" 947858628469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 253860ef-d859-44b9-af2b-fc6d279b0e1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858629447","data":{"timestamp":" 947858629446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 253860ef-d859-44b9-af2b-fc6d279b0e1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858630458","data":{"timestamp":" 947858630457"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 253860ef-d859-44b9-af2b-fc6d279b0e1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858630810","data":{"timestamp":" 947858630810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 253860ef-d859-44b9-af2b-fc6d279b0e1e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858646009","data":{"timestamp":" 947858646007"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJA"," userResponse":" TAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858649293","data":{"timestamp":" 947858649292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMU"," userResponse":" TAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858652567","data":{"timestamp":" 947858652566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tawi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAWI"," userResponse":" TAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858655837","data":{"timestamp":" 947858655837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858658584","data":{"timestamp":" 947858658583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANI"," userResponse":" TANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858662067","data":{"timestamp":" 947858662066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAJI"," userResponse":" TAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858665568","data":{"timestamp":" 947858665567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAKA"," userResponse":" TAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858668865","data":{"timestamp":" 947858668864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858671594","data":{"timestamp":" 947858671593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYA"," userResponse":" TAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ta.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858675297","data":{"timestamp":" 947858675296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" taya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858675651","data":{"timestamp":" 947858675650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" d94907cc-9ff4-4da9-9c66-7d675893bdfd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ta.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" taya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYA"," userResponse":" TAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858692633","data":{"timestamp":" 947858692633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858697778","data":{"timestamp":" 947858697777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858703832","data":{"timestamp":" 947858703832"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858709889","data":{"timestamp":" 947858709888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858715751","data":{"timestamp":" 947858715750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858721481","data":{"timestamp":" 947858721480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858727043","data":{"timestamp":" 947858727043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858732750","data":{"timestamp":" 947858732749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858738417","data":{"timestamp":" 947858738416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858745777","data":{"timestamp":" 947858745776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 16e46982-c35e-44ae-9c6e-b29212889719"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858763760","data":{"timestamp":" 947858763758"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858770629","data":{"timestamp":" 947858770628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858781857","data":{"timestamp":" 947858781856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858787567","data":{"timestamp":" 947858787567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858793505","data":{"timestamp":" 947858793505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858798745","data":{"timestamp":" 947858798745"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858804279","data":{"timestamp":" 947858804278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858809674","data":{"timestamp":" 947858809673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858815601","data":{"timestamp":" 947858815600"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858821395","data":{"timestamp":" 947858821394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858828769","data":{"timestamp":" 947858828768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" e5686944-cdb3-4edf-9618-021d92035375"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858853131","data":{"timestamp":" 947858853130"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858864160","data":{"timestamp":" 947858864159"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-kile-jani"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858876946","data":{"timestamp":" 947858876946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_lina-yale-tawi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858888123","data":{"timestamp":" 947858888122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-ubao-nanu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858899067","data":{"timestamp":" 947858899066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858910006","data":{"timestamp":" 947858909995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858920161","data":{"timestamp":" 947858920160"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamu_tamu-wivu-yawe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamu"," userResponse":" tamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858930617","data":{"timestamp":" 947858930617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858941106","data":{"timestamp":" 947858941105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-nchi-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858952868","data":{"timestamp":" 947858952867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858959246","data":{"timestamp":" 947858959240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" aa0efd8b-e1b7-485a-af66-32be7ae9d290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858985389","data":{"timestamp":" 947858985388"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-pini-goli"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947858996448","data":{"timestamp":" 947858996447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_tawi-ubao-nanu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859007218","data":{"timestamp":" 947859007217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tatu_tatu-anga-ziwe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tatu"," userResponse":" tatu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859018154","data":{"timestamp":" 947859018154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_taya-kile-jani"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859031414","data":{"timestamp":" 947859031414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taya_tani-taya-paka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taya"," userResponse":" taya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859042739","data":{"timestamp":" 947859042738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_taka_taka-lori-hapo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" taka"," userResponse":" taka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859053651","data":{"timestamp":" 947859053650"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-kiti-wako"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859064932","data":{"timestamp":" 947859064931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tamu_tamu-wivu-yawe"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tamu"," userResponse":" tamu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859075702","data":{"timestamp":" 947859075700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tano_tano-nchi-ziwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tano"," userResponse":" tano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859087627","data":{"timestamp":" 947859087627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_lina-yale-tawi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tawi"," userResponse":" tawi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ta.show.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859093970","data":{"timestamp":" 947859093967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 00e5d562-ba5d-43c3-bed9-98d59729627c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ta.show.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tawi_lina-yale-tawi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859115291","data":{"timestamp":" 947859115289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 30b8d8af-d788-4d8b-a1a0-a91d2c6eafeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859115553","data":{"timestamp":" 947859115553"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 30b8d8af-d788-4d8b-a1a0-a91d2c6eafeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859116532","data":{"timestamp":" 947859116531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 30b8d8af-d788-4d8b-a1a0-a91d2c6eafeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859117845","data":{"timestamp":" 947859117844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 30b8d8af-d788-4d8b-a1a0-a91d2c6eafeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947859118538","data":{"timestamp":" 947859118538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_164834"," gameId":" 30b8d8af-d788-4d8b-a1a0-a91d2c6eafeb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}